FELIPE GARCIA SUEZ

25/10/2000

Location:

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Phone:

+54 (0)341 366 - 9925

Email:

garciasuezfelipe@gmail.com

Summary

Full Stack Developer. I have experiences in projects using Node, React-Redux, Sequelize and Express mainly focused on e-commerce. I am passionate about everything focused on user experience and I highlight for my ability to identify problems and my adaptation to the workflo. Knowledge of hardware with experience in the crypto world.

Experience

Hardware technician – 06/2021 – 08/2022

CryptoRig is an enterprise formed between partners whose objective is the assembly and maintenance of crypto mining rigs. Working in this branch made me acquire knowledge based on the crypto world and the following qualities:

- Experience with computer hardware problems and operating system management.
- Work based on a time limit and specifications defined by the client, know how to treat it to keep it satisfied.
- Work as a team and make the company prosper and progress.

soyHenry final project – September 2022

The **KEMBA** is a shoe e-commerce made up of a group of 5 people. It is a fully functional page made with react & redux, node.js, sequelize and express using SCRUM methodology, that has the possibility to buy products with a payment gateway included and a detailed view for the product owner that shows sales, users and statistics.

My work was focused on the routes of the backend and the construction of the database, which is what interests me the most.

Freelancer - September 2022 - Present

I had the chance to sell projects as a freelancer through SCRUM methodology, most of them using React-Redux on the front-end. Doing these jobs gave me the chance to understand the market of web programming and the commitment to the client to supply their order.

Education

Secondary: San Juan Bautista De La Salle 2013-2018

Bachelor of Economics and Administration.

soyHenry Full Stack Developer course +400 hours

Full-time course adapted to the labor market with teaching and practices in JavaScript, CSS, React, Redux, Node, Seguelize, Express and PostgreSQL.

Languages

English Intermidiate – C2 by EFSET certificate 77/100

I can understand reading and make simple conversations. I see myself as fully capable of managing myself in an English-speaking environment.